Guide to the Allan R. Holmberg collection on Peru, circa 1946-1966.
Holmberg, Allan R., collection on Peru, circa 1946-1966
- Separated Materials
  - Plano del Local Escolar de Vicos Provincia de Carhuaz-Ancash Construido por el Proyecto Peru-Cornell, October 1954; Series II. Cornell Peru Project (Accession 2): Vicos-Education, 1950s (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - Topographical maps [2], Cordillera Blanca, 1932, 1939; Series II. Cornell Peru Project (Accession 2): Maps, 1932, 1939 (Mapcase-folder 8)
  - Plano del Local Escolar, undated; Series II. Cornell Peru Project (Accession 2): Vicos-Education, 1950s (Box 14)